S-Since when were you...
Water sploosh...
You know this?
I think I know, I don't think I know.
I don't think I know that I know.
I think I know even though
I don't think I know...
Which is it?!
Hey!
Hey Spike, where the hell are we?!
Isn't it Earth?
Earth?!
Hey, this ship was headed for Mars!
Why the hell are we on Earth
all of a sudden?!
Dunno.
Shit, this isn't funny.
While we're wasting time, our fugitive...!
It was the first big one in a while.
In any case why the hell are we on—?
Jet.
The women are gone.
Listen, if you lead me to that "water sploosh"
place, I'll give you something good.
Good thing? What?
Something very, tremendously,
wonderfully good.
wonderfully good!
Hot!
Hot! Hot! Hot! Hot!
This!
Water sploosh!
I knew I shouldn't have trusted you...
Hey, I found Ed!
Ed has been found?
What, you know them?
35 point 38 point 0, 35 point
48 point 1, 35 point 48 point 2...
This!
This, this, this!
Hey, can I have your nails?
N-Nails?
I'm collecting them!
Can I, please?
Just the pinky one will do!
35 point 52 point 3, 35 point...
This, this!
Come on... can I have it? Please?
What are you guys?!
Hey!
Ed?!
Is that really you... Ed?
I'm sorry about that.
That's the best way
to make the kids listen.
It's all right.
Is Ed from this place?
She wandered in about five years ago.
Before I knew it, she was eating with us
as if it had always been that way.
And about three years ago,
she wandered away.
As if she was a cat or something.
I was wondering how she
was doing nowadays,
but I didn't think she
would suddenly appear.
All right, it's time to eat!
Dear Lord up in the heavens...
Never mind the rest. Let's eat!
Let's eat!
I have to get going now...
What, you can stay longer, right?
I'm actually looking for something...
Ed knows where it is.
We just came here for food.
You...
You have to gimme something good!
Oh yeah, Ed.
There's something good in
the desk drawer over there.
Something good?
Go get it.
Something good!
Inside that drawer.
Not that.
Yeah, that. Open it!
Her father.
Whose?
He came looking for Ed about 2 months ago.
He said he forgot that he
had put her in an orphanage
and that he had been looking for
7 years, hopping around the world.
I hope she will be able to meet him...
People have to cherish what ties they have...
Yeah!
Are you... Faye?
Impossible...
Really?
It's me, Sally Yung!
I was in your high school
graduating class!
Are you all right?
I was really surprised.
I thought you were a ghost.
You look just like back then...
You know, they say ghosts appear in
places where they have regrets...
Oh, yeah, I remember now.
You were put in cold sleep
after that accident.
And that's why you
look like back then...
Accident?
You don't remember, Faye?
I...
Grandma!
Grandma, we gotta go back now.
Is it that time already?
Do you know who this is?
I bet you don't know. Actually, she's...
A ghost.
Goodbye. Take care.
Hey, you guys!
What's with this course
change without asking?!
Our plans have all been
screwed because of it!
I don't appreciate you
doing things on your own!
You want to smell something really good?
What's with them?
What are they being so secretive about?
Leave them alone.
Maybe they're too hungry
for their own good...
Humans go insane if they don't eat food.
50 million?
I see... pretty big.
Appledelhi Siniz Hesap Lutfen.
Would you like one, Mackenroe?
That's Macintire.
No thank you, Mr. Appledelhi.
You sure? Eggs are good.
As they say, power and charge.
That's what's important, Macintosh.
That's Macintire.
Why is it that you can't ever
remember your assistant's name?
Hm, don't worry about
the small things in life.
Hurry, Macky-Mike!
That's Macintire!
Watch where you're going!
Hey?
Sorry...
Sorry?
I-I...
I have to go...
Going out?
Where are you going?
I finally remembered where I belong.
Where you belong?
You have someone waiting for you, too.
You have somewhere you belong.
You should go look for it, too.
That's the best thing, you know...
This one is a piece of cake.
50 million is right there!
If they can eat sukiyaki
filled with meat, then they—
Faye went out.
Again? Where the hell did she go this time?
A woman's heart and
the skies of Ganymede, was it?
You're Appledelhi?
Can you come along with us?
Cooperate with us if you
don't wanna get hurt.
Who are you guys?
Don't interrupt our work!
Work?
What does this Earth need
to regain a peaceful peace?
This Earth of wild chaos! Is it the cosmos?
That is a map! A map!
Yes, happiness comes in the form of a map!
We are creating maps to save the Earth!
A map?
But, meteors fall often
and change the landscape.
That's why we're globetrotting.
We're chasing after every meteor!
Until every single meteor falls onto Earth!
Enough with the excuses!
You!
I wasn't expecting someone this adept.
Is that you, Ed?!
That's enough! Stop!
Françoise!
How's that?
And that, and that?
This is father-person.
Father?
Your father?
She had such a thing?
This is Spike-person and Jet-person.
I see.
No, father. Good people.
Oh? I see.
Thank you for taking care of my son.
Or was it daughter?
Oh well, it's all right either way.
That's a token of my appreciation.
Then Ed, were you the one
who put the bounty on?
Fifty point zero, zero,
zero, zero, zero, zero?
Only 50 Woolongs?
So, you wanna come with me?
Hurry, Michael-duck!
That's Macintire!
Hey, wait!
Father!
He's gone.
Hey, it's dinner time...
Spike, dinner.
You can't come with me, Ein.
Ed is going someplace far, far away.
I might not be coming back.
So Ein, you should go back home.
Do you want to come with Ed?
Let's go, Ein!
aishiteta to nageku niwa
Too much time has passed by
amarinimo toki wa sugite shimatta
to lament that we were deeply in love
mada kokoro no hokorobi wo
The wind keeps blowing, while my heart
iyasenu mama kaze ga fuiteru
cannot heal all the tears in it
kawaita hitomi de dareka naite kure
Someone, cry for me with parched eyes
The real folk blues
honto no kanashimi ga shiritai dake
I only want to know what true sadness is
doro no kawa ni tsukatta
Sitting in muddy water
jinsei mo waruku wa nai
isn't such a bad life
ichido kiri de owaru nara
if it ends after the first time
Everything has a beginning... and an end.
Life is just a cycle of them.
With unwanted endings, becoming an adult
is to experience the inevitable finale.
It's been a fast trip for Bebop,
with only two episodes left.
But make sure you pay
close attention to how it ends.
Next episode: The Real Folk Blues (Part 1).