Those who don't work, don't eat.
Go find your own food.
Me? I'm okay.
Women are grand by birth.
3 million...
Well, I'll have the guys earn it for me.
Damn, blues harp music is good.
It's just as good as I thought.
I thought you were a fan of jazz music?
Don't be stupid.
I even warbled when I was
sucking on my mother's milk!
You were a pretty thoughtful kid.
No mistake, that's Giraffe.
All right, I'm going from the right.
You go from the left.
There's a fatso in the way.
That's... Fatty.
The ball's in your court.
Hey, Fatty!
Fatty River! Long time no see!
Oh! Who'd have thought, it's Jet Black!
When the hell did you get here?
How about you? You look so easygoing!
Did ya catch a big one?
I didn't know you were a fan of blues music.
You're kidding me.
I've lived only for the blues
since I was in my dad's sack!
Give him back!
Zebra!
Hey you! Don't die!
Hey!
Shit, are you going to wipe out my bounty?
D-Don't be fooled by his appearance...
You idiot! Don't speak!
...him... Help...
...him...
This stone...
Hey!
I can't say for sure until I analyze it,
but it might be worth a hefty sum.
So, what are ya gonna do?
Like I know?
He's the one who gave it to me and
He's the one who went off and died.
I see no harm in keeping it.
There is no harm.
After all, it's not your duty to help the kid.
This is gonna pay for our food.
There's none for you.
You have such a poor heart.
I'm not like that.
Here, have a gift.
Oh, what's this?
An invoice? What for?
All the expenses that you've
racked up on our ship.
Thanks for your business!
You're welcome.
So why are you asking
about the dead bounty?
Well... uh...
So you were after Giraffe, too.
Ya got a good deal?
Go ahead, eat.
Ah well. There's no bounty in it anyway.
Yeah. No gain at all.
No, no. There really is nothing.
Ah well. You'll owe me one for today.
You know that kid on the
blues harp the other day?
Giraffe was after that kid Wen's father.
His old acquaintance, Zebra.
Acquaintance?
You didn't even know that?
That they were the top of the Volunteer
Self Defense Squad until ten years ago?
But why is he after an old comrade?
Ten years ago, Zebra and Giraffe
attempted to reclaim a certain facility.
But, a few days later, Zebra ends up missing
and Giraffe finds himself blindfolded
in a weird place he'd never seen before.
Giraffe was going after the top spot
in the group, but he was betrayed.
But Zebra was still alive.
So, in the end, Giraffe was
killed by some form of betrayal?
Women easily betray others,
but men live for duty.
Duty, huh?
That's what I'd like to believe.
Who are you?
Someone suspicious.
What do you want?
Giraffe asked me
to help you.
But Zebra shot Giraffe.
Yeah...
Then why did Giraffe tell him to help the kid?
Hm? This kid's showing up here, too.
He must be pretty famous.
Yeah. The kid's a genius.
Huh?
Hey! This guy isn't Zebra!
What?!
Look... the date!
What the—?!
Why the hell is this kid in an article
from 30 years ago with the same face?!
Come on. There's nothing to fear.
Come over here.
Little twerps should stay outta this.
If you stick your neck
in too far, you'll get burnt.
Don't give me that
conceited crap, kid.
I ain't a kid.
All kids say that.
I may look like this, but I've been alive since the days when humans
crawled only on the face of the Earth.
It started on the day of the accidental
explosion of the hyperspace gate.
My body has ceased to age.
I can't die.
The guys that took interest in me,
and experimented on me, all died before me.
The end for this guy started
when he snuck into the lab.
I needed a "parent" to use as a cover.
D-Don't be fooled by his appearance...
...him...
Help...
I think this was the third guy.
Now, gimme the ring.
Ring? What ring?
That's fine...
Even if you had it, it's a pearl before swine.
Give me a break, you big klutz!
You're lucky you got away with this little
since we don't have
the money for a funeral!
Sorry.
Knock it off, Ein!
Shut up.
Oh?
Jet, the alpha-catch.
Shit... this piece of junk.
All right!
Now... what are ya seein'?
The hotel.
He's remembering the time that Giraffe died.
Give him back! Zebra!
Come over here!
Shit!
And then what?
What did Giraffe say?!
I have it now. I can do you in with this.
This is a stone that will return time to you!
Now, hand Zebra over to me!
Zebra!
When the Gate exploded,
a vast amount of energy and
an imaginary coordinate system
were created from the
resulting twists in hyperspace and
got enclosed into the gem of this ring.
And that same energy broke
Wen's circadian rhythm.
His pineal gland continually
produces a substance
similar to melatonin that inhibits aging.
That's how the theory goes in a nutshell...
You understand?
Like I do...
I don't either.
So, in other words,
there's no way to make sure
other than to stick that gem into Wen.
I don't know what will happen.
It might explode the moment you shoot it in.
This makes me excited.
What?
I thought this might be the last time
I'd see you, so I thought I'd see you off.
Oh, so you're finally going to leave us?
No, you aren't coming back.
I don't like it.
I don't like it one bit.
Men are such idiots...
I see...
I can finally die now...
I feel so heavy...
But... I feel so at ease now.
Do you know?
Do you understand? Do you...
Like I do...
aishiteta to nageku niwa
Too much time has passed by
amarinimo toki wa sugite shimatta
to lament that we were deeply in love
mada kokoro no hokorobi wo
The wind keeps blowing, while my heart
iyasenu mama kaze ga fuiteru
cannot heal all the tears in it
kawaita hitomi de dareka naite kure
Someone, cry for me with parched eyes
The real folk blues
honto no kanashimi ga shiritai dake
I only want to know what true sadness is
doro no kawa ni tsukatta
Sitting in muddy water
jinsei mo waruku wa nai
isn't such a bad life
ichido kiri de owaru nara
if it ends after the first time
Hey, do you know
what heavy metal is?!
What?! I didn't catch that!
Heavy metal, I said, heavy metal!
What did you say?!
Hey, can you do something
about this racket?!
This is running in the background
during the entire next episode!
Maybe I shouldn't appear, then!
I can't hear a damn thing you're saying!
Next episode: Heavy Metal Queen!
Are you sure they can really hear us?!