And so, the turtle took him to a place
called Ryuuguujou as a reward.
Ryuuguujou?
Yeah. At that palace,
they held a welcome party for him.
Beautiful women, and scrumptious feasts.
Breams and halibut swam about,
and so he spent his time as if in a dream.
I see...
I haven't eaten breams or
halibut in quite a while...
Days passed before he knew it,
and when he was about to go back,
he was given the Tamatebako as a souvenir.
Tamatebako? Is that yummy?
It's not food. It's a chest
with treasure inside.
I haven't seen any treasure
in quite a while either...
You guys are so tasteless.
This is an old fantasy tale!
The turtle's Tamatebako...
What were you listening to?
I should quit the horses now.
Pay up 6300 woolongs.
What, where did that come from?
This was for you.
For... me?
C.O.D. Even.
To top it off, no return address.
I had no choice but to accept it...
Hey! Wait!
Hey! What about the 6300 woolongs?!
Busy woman.
Could it be a collection agency
from the life extension firm?
Or...
No, could it be...
Oooh... I just have too
many things it could be...
So for now, I'll just run away!
Don't you think it's fishy?
For a woman who always claims
other people's property
as her own to run away
without even touching it?
She seems to have picked up a lot
of grudges from all over, though.
I should do an explosives test and
a biochemical test just in case...
No! I should return this to
the courier service
and have them refund
the money I paid for her sake...
Hey, Spike!
What the hell is this?
Does it make any ticking noises?
Nope.
I got data!
Data from the courier service!
The sender is...
A nonprofit nunnery in Europa?!
There's more...
Pluto Prison?
Asteroid Actors' Studio?
Fourth Uranus Observatory?
Venus News Network?
Forwarded, forwarded,
and forwarded some more...
This thing's been passed around
the entire solar system.
Here.
Due to the explosion of the Lunar Gate,
all data from before 2022 has been lost.
An antique.
It seems to be something called a videotape.
An artifact of the good old days.
She's the one that ran away.
She has no right to complain
even if we sell it off.
You think it will sell?
They say he's a maniac when it
comes to 20th century images...
I'm sure he'd buy it.
I just don't think this is worth anything.
The real worth of treasures like this
can't be determined from the outside.
You may be surprised at how
much you can sell it for!
I need to get enough to cover
the C.O.D. Charges at least.
Excuse me!
So...
Quiet!
Everything about this city is different
from Minnesota, where we were before.
Hey, brother, are you sure
we can get along well here?
Mm... To tell the truth,
I wasn't so sure that we could.
But, I'm sure we'll be all right.
Because I'm here with my twin sister.
Thanks, brother.
Oh man, I have to work in the morning!
Good night, brother.
Good night!
God, that's good! Drama series
from the 20th century are so good!
On the other hand...
Drama series as of late are so...
I have something you want to watch—
Hey, hey, hey, you can't do that!
The cigarette, man, the cigarette!
Don't you know that smoke can totally
screw up electrical appliances?
Sheesh, this is why I hate
people who don't know...
Idiot, idiot, idiot, idiot! Sheesh!
What the hell do you guys want?!
What do you have against me?!
No grudges, but no gratitude, either.
I just have something we
want you to buy from us.
Ah! Is that a Beta cassette?!
That's amazing!
Where did you get a hold of this?
This is a true find, mister!
It's close to a miracle that
this thing exists in one piece!
Beta?
You don't know what this is?
Oh, all right, do you want me to explain?
Back in the 20th Century, they didn't
use disks like we do to record movies.
They used things called video tapes,
which are in cassettes like this.
It's not digital! It's analog!
And to top it off,
it's magnetic... Yeah, magnetic!
They were recording with electromagnetic
signals! Ain't that amazing?
But a disagreement between
the companies who created
this technology resulted in
two standards, Beta and VHS.
Beta had a small cassette for their day,
and the playback decks were compact
and didn't take much space.
You didn't get much noise when using special features like freeze frame and slow-mo.
And, because Beta had high quality images,
users who were into good graphics
supported it really heavily.
But, there begins the unfortunate
history of the Beta tape.
You don't need to tell me.
Huh? This is just the introduction!
I told you what we wanted.
So how is it? Are ya gonna buy it?
Well, that depends on what's on it...
Hey, what's wrong?
It's so hard to adjust the tracking
for these early Beta tapes...
This way?
Or this way?
It's eating the tape!
It's not getting any better...
It's coming...
It is... It is...
I got it!
Dogs are better than horses after all!
Most things get better if I kick 'em.
You just don't know when to quit.
Dammit, repay me for breaking my deck!
You again...
You broke someone else's
valuable machinery
and you're not going to
take responsibility for it?!
And how are you going to take
responsibility for our valuable tape?
Early Beta decks often eat tapes!
In any case, I'll have you
pay for the repair costs!
We'll call it even with
the cost of the tape!
What?! Beta—
Sheesh...
Hello, Beta deck!
There's just one of those.
Where is this?
The Underground City
Electrical Museum in old Asia?
I'm going to figure out what's
on that tape at any cost!
Is it really something worth all the trouble?
It's coming... It's... It's... It's...
Yeah! I got it!
Really, I wonder if those guys were
sucking up all my luck all this time.
Ah... Hello.
Hello?
Hey, helllllloooooo...
Ah... it's... Faye... Yoohoo...
Wait...
Hello? What is this, where are you guys?
Earth...
Earth!
Earth?!
Wait a minute, you guys left me
behind to go that far away...
Spike... and Jet...
All right, just a little longer.
Is there really one left in a place like this?
Nothing ventured, nothing gained.
28th underground floor.
It's not moving?
The cable broke, so it's stuck.
Why are we going through all of this?
It just means that
treasure-hunting isn't easy.
Treasure?
What was the treasure we were after?
The Tamatebako, was it?
I kinda see why the man
turned into an old geezer
after opening the Tamatebako now.
Even if we head back now,
we're not gonna be any younger.
This is some Ryuuguujou...
Where did that broad go
in the first place?!
It's coming... It's, it's...
Oh well, nothing I could've done.
Races are all luck anyway.
Is it here?
It's here.
All right.
Is this it?
Yeah, that's gotta be it.
And?
Which one are we taking back?
Let's see...
Well, bigger is always better, they say.
What's wrong?
The size...
Isn't it all right?
It's not going in.
Force it in.
But...
Ah! That's not it!
That's VHS, so
ya can't see the tape!
Oh, hello, it's me.
Ein, who are you talking to?
Oh, it's Faye!
I'm glad there's an organism
there that I can talk to.
What is it?
Was there anyone who went
there to visit me?
Visitors?
Like scary middle-aged guys.
You know, guys that scream stuff like
"Gimme back my money!"
Or "You're under arrest!"?
Yeah there was one.
Eh? And?
Something about repay him, even with
tape munch, munch and grind, bye-bye!
Eh? Okay...
Oh, well.
Where's Spike and Jet?
Disappointed and zoned out.
I see...
Hmm...
That's how...
Oh, well.
If they're so lonely without me,
I guess I have no choice.
I'm coming back!
What?! Another package for that broad?!
I won't accept it! Take it and go back!
Shit, why do I have to pay for her C.O.D?!
And not once, but twice!
You sure are persistent.
A Beta!
We can see the tape with this?
Yeah.
Hey guys, long time no see.
It's done.
Hold up.
If you're going to watch,
pay back the C.O.D. Charges.
With tax, a total of 31,500 woolongs.
Oh, fine.
We have something!
Ooooh... what's this?
Shut up and watch.
Um...
Everyone decided to
send a message to themselves
ten years in the future.
Oh, come on, don't laugh!
Um...
This makes me blush after all!
Eh? Something I want to say?
Good morning...
Oh! Never mind!
Good morning, me.
Did you sleep well?
And did you wake up well?
Does the light and the wind,
the air and the smell, all feel brand new?
Is each and every cell
in your body awake now?
Today, you are who you are today.
You are a newer version of me.
Myself ten years from now...
That's so far away for me that
I can't even begin to imagine.
Am I alone?
Or is there a wonderful person next to me?
Well, knowing me, I'm sure I am
troubling a lot of different people.
But that's all right. There's no problem.
I will always be cheering you on.
And now for a big cheer...
from the bottom of my heart.
Go! Go!
Me, me, me!
Do your best, do your best! Me, me, me!
Don't lose, don't lose! Me, me, me!
I don't know...
I can't remember...
Is this...
me?
I am no longer here.
But I'm here today, and I'll always
be cheering for you right here.
Cheering for you, my only self.
aishiteta to nageku niwa
Too much time has passed by
amarinimo toki wa sugite shimatta
to lament that we were deeply in love
mada kokoro no hokorobi wo
The wind keeps blowing, while my heart
iyasenu mama kaze ga fuiteru
cannot heal all the tears in it
kawaita hitomi de dareka naite kure
Someone, cry for me with parched eyes
The real folk blues
honto no kanashimi ga shiritai dake
I only want to know what true sadness is
doro no kawa ni tsukatta
Sitting in muddy water
jinsei mo waruku wa nai
isn't such a bad life
ichido kiri de owaru nara
if it ends after the first time
You know, I'm starting to get tired of
us doing all the previews like this.
Once in a while, can't we
have someone else...
Oh? Oh! You're perfect. All right!
Here, you try doing it this time.
Oh! So, that's how it is!
Wow, this is going to be
an interesting episode!
Next Episode: Wild Horses.
Hey, it spoke!