Space travel log 0968.
We were wasting our free time.
It sounds good to call the
bounty-hunting job a "freelance" job,
but all that means is that we're self-employed.
When we have no jobs, we have none at all.
Well, that's all a part of our destiny,
but it's troublesome that we're out of money.
And so, we get urges to make quick cash...
Any problem with using these?
Evens!
Evens, is it?
No, odds after all!
Odds, is it?
Yeah... odds.
Double ace, even.
I can't eat any more...
Well, it would be easiest for me
if you paid up in cash.
So, what'll it be?
A man does not take back his word!
That's why I told you not to do it.
Humans were meant to work and
sweat for their money after all.
Those that try to get rich quick
or live at the expense of others
all get divine retribution
somewhere along the way.
That is the lesson...
But one thing about humans is that they
quickly forget the
lessons they just learned.
Dammit.
There was a fridge way back here?
"Survival of the fittest" is the law of the land.
To fool and to be fooled is the reason we live.
I've never had anything good
happen to me when I trust others.
That's the lesson.
How much did you swindle?
Would you stop saying things
that would hurt my reputation?
He lost on his own!
Because he couldn't
see through this cheat?
It's part of one's skill to see through it.
At least give his clothes back to him.
I'll lend them to him.
Greedy, aren't we?
It's rough out there in the real world.
Hey, what's up?
Something bit me.
What do you mean, "something"?
It wasn't a rat!
Look at this! This wound on my neck!
Hey!
This is silly. It was a waste
of time running over here.
Spike! I was bitten around that fridge!
Fridge?
Hmm? You have a clue?
I'm sure... there was something...
Nope, can't remember.
You sure this is gonna work?
It works on everything but
myopia and cavities.
Then it works on athlete's foot?
Of course.
Don't you have something more
legit that would get rid of sores?
That would be this.
That gets rid of sores?
Yeah.
Crush this, and you boil it
in 3 cups of water until
the liquid simmers down
to 1 cup, and you drink it.
Spike, isn't there something more...
different?
Oh, I got just the thing.
Yeah, gimme that.
Gimme what you had before.
Hey... I'm feeling a lot sicker now...
Do I look pale?
You're pretty pale to begin with.
What is this awful smell?
Herbal medicine.
Herbal medicine? This?
It smells like you just left a rag
that cleaned up spilt milk out to dry!
I think it's more like rotten soybeans.
Knock it off! I have to drink this ya know!
Oh brother.
Hey now, this goes too far for a joke...
It was a rat, right?
There's nothing to make a fuss about.
Am I wrong?
I have no clue.
He seems to have gotten some poison
that's not in this database.
Looking at similar poisons...
Cryptosporidium...
That's not it.
Cholera?
Nope.
Ebola virus?
Bifidobacterium?
Not even close.
What is it?
Ein, you're being noisy.
I can say for sure that
it wasn't an ordinary rat.
Hey, keep it quiet.
So what is it?
Well, it's...
A mysterious space creature!
Spooky! The attack of
a horrible space creature!
Oh yeah, there's that possibility...
Heh... Yeah, right.
Then what is it?
It's not in the database.
Yeah...
These base-pairs are weird, too.
You think so?
We've never seen symptoms
like this before either.
Other than a space creature,
what is it? What is it?
Well... um, perhaps something like
a rat went through a mutation
and evolved into some mysterious creature
and carried a mysterious poison...
What's that about?
That isn't too different from the
"mysterious space creature" theory!
This is too silly.
Aiya... what are we gonna do, Ein?
It's a space creature!
It's spooky!
All right. This is made to sense heat sources.
It's usually used to find
bounties that are hiding.
Can you see me?
All right, I'm gonna test it,
so move just like I tell you.
Ein! Where are you going?
Hey, wait!
Hey!
That's weird... Is it broken?
Was that response from you?
That story you were telling, about some mysterious creature or something or other...
Oh, yeah.
What happens if you're bitten?
I can't say for sure until we catch
the creature, but I'm going to guess...
...death?
No... why did it have to be this way?
I still have a lot to live for...
I haven't committed any crimes...
I'm still young and lively...
Lively?
Oh, poor little me!
Hey now, why are you getting into this?
August 6th. Skyday.
Today, we will go look for the
spooky mysterious space creature.
Lesson, lesson... if you
see a stranger, follow him!
Are you here?
Are you here, Mr. Spooky creature?
Ed! Ein!
Hey! This isn't hide-and-seek!
Exploration, experimentation, exclamation.
Lights shine bright in the many towns.
I will come back alive.
I trust you, Ed.
Ein!
Are ya in here?
You're not in here?
Answer me!
Really...
Ein, Ed! What happened?
Ein!
Hey, hang in there!
Where's Ed?
I can't believe it got you this easily.
You're a dog! Where're
your natural instincts?!
No choice... Guess I'm going in!
Cruising down Route 66.
Approximate cruising time left: 82 hours.
From here, we will enter full autopilot.
After passing the gate, this ship
will automatically land on Mars.
The route cannot be
changed after confirmation.
Ed! You aren't here, are you? Hey!
Did that thing get her, too?
Don't surprise me!
I've been waiting for ya!
Excellent!
Come on, you slime!
Got 'im!
This thing seems familiar...
I guess I shoulda eaten that.
Oh yeah, it should be in the fridge—
That was when I remembered everything.
It was... oh, one year ago.
When I had gotten ahold of a real lobster,
I hid it in the fridge in this stockroom
just so nobody else would eat it.
But I had forgotten about it,
and left it in there for a whole year.
I wonder what it looks like in there now...
Shit!
Dammit!
You shouldn't leave things in the fridge.
That is the lesson.
Sweet bean roll!
Mmm... can't eat anymore...
aishiteta to nageku niwa
Too much time has passed by
amarinimo toki wa sugite shimatta
to lament that we were deeply in love
mada kokoro no hokorobi wo
The wind keeps blowing, while my heart
iyasenu mama kaze ga fuiteru
cannot heal all the tears in it
kawaita hitomi de dareka naite kure
Someone, cry for me with parched eyes
The real folk blues
honto no kanashimi ga shiritai dake
I only want to know what true sadness is
doro no kawa ni tsukatta
Sitting in muddy water
jinsei mo waruku wa nai
isn't such a bad life
ichido kiri de owaru nara
if it ends after the first time
And so... they all passed away.
Everyone, it was brief,
but thanks for your support.
This was the last episode.
I hope they rest in peace.
Amen.
And starting next episode,
we bring you "Cowgirl Ed"!
I'm the main character!
Hey, wait a minute!
What kinda selfish crap is that?!
Next episode: Jupiter Jazz, part 1.
There really is another episode!